<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amrit Raj Vardhan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amrit Raj Vardhan</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Heatmap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/heatmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:59:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/heatmap/</guid>
      <description>&#xD;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversational Agent Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/f1-conversational-agent-rabbit-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/f1-conversational-agent-rabbit-hole/</guid>
      <description>F1 Data Conversational Agent So my basic idea is to create a &amp;ldquo;chatbot?&amp;rdquo; for F1 that fetches live data, answers a user query, from OpenF1 and answers questions about all-things-f1. Here are the links I am going through.&#xA;inner thought - hmmm, maybe I need to create architectural decisions right now, some UMLs etc.&#xA;inner demon - Naah bro, this is a self project, who cares about these stuff.&#xA;API with Conversational Agent all-MiniLM-L6-v2 SBERT </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Conversational Agents - Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>This is the iteration 1 for creating and understanding Agentic views of Conversational AIs. Agentic AIs have recently shown to outperform LLMs alone. MoA has recently beaten GPT-4o.&#xA;I installed Ollama, pulled Lllama-3 8b, read about crewai, played around with Agents and their respective Tools, Actions, Tasks. I plan to extensively use it for my own applications.&#xA;Below is the code for the implementaiton&#xA;from crewai import Task, Agent, Crew, Process from crewai_tools import tool from langchain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Everything</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/all-things-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/all-things-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>This is a question bank for Machine Learning/Deep Learning/Data Science roles. Over time, I will try to sort this on topics and increasing difficulty.&#xA;Last update &amp;mdash; 17/07/2024 &amp;mdash;&#xA;Explain Machine learning in Layman terms. - Tags [Basic Machine Learning, ] Machine Learning is a branch of Data Science that uses algorithms and tries to fit in a function to already given data points so as to better predict an unseen observable data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Links for Hugo based static website deployed in Github Pages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/deploying-this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/deploying-this-website/</guid>
      <description>These are the walkthroughs/links that helped me deploy this website on Github Pages.&#xA;I procrastinate a lot, so I googled along the lines of &amp;ldquo;Best blog hosted on Github Pages&amp;rdquo; and I chose the first thing I stumbled upon, which was, Archie theme under Hugo.&#xA;Hugo installation can be followed here&#xA;Installed hugo locally and started working on setting up the website locally before deploying it on Github Pages. I had to copy all the files present in themes/archie folder to the root folder after cloning the repo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Amrit. I am a software developer by profession. I am interested in Machine Learning, Deep Learning, and the field of Data Science.&#xA;I have a Masters in Computer Science from University of Illinois, Chicago. I worked in Barclays after my undergrad as a SWE for 3+ years. I helped save my organization, cut costs by automating multiple processes. I have developed multiple end-to-end software solutions that required me to do architectural decisions, which included, but not limited to, making Proof-of-concepts, SDD/PDDs, development plan, leading teams, talking to shareholders, developing/coding, doing SITs/UATs, deploying the code in production and providing Level3 support according to the SLA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
